Juan Navas

Full Stack Developer

I'm a Full Stack Developer and Computer Science student. I have experience with each layer of web development: frontend, backend, database. Also, I build mobile applications with React Native, Flutter. I'm passionate about technology, never stop learning.

Work Experience

Intermediate Full Stack Developer

Teravision

February 2021 - June 2021 Frontend developer with Next.js.

Developer

Glufco

January 2021 - February 2021 Full stack developer with Vue.js, Laravel and PostgreSQL.

Full Stack Developer

Freelance

May 2020 - January 2021

Full stack developer building some projects with React.js, Node.js, Typescript, MongoDB, Flutter, React Native.

Programmer

FYSS

August 2018 - April 2020

Full stack developer building some projects with React.js, Node.js, Laravel, MySQL, MongoDB, Docker, Web3.js.

Education

Bachelor of Computer Science Central University of Venezuela

2022

Contact Details

Phone: <u>+584266470654</u>
Email: <u>iam@juannavas.dev</u>
Visit: <u>juannavas.dev</u>
LinkedIn: <u>juannavasjn</u>
Github: <u>juannavasjn</u>
Gitlab: <u>juannavasjn</u>

Professional Skills

Team player
Problem solving
Software development

Software Skills

Git
Docker
React.js
Node.js
React Native
Flutter
GraphQL
Laravel
AWS, GCP

Personal Skills

Spanish Language
English Language
Effective communication